(Scene:)Mrs. Davis.
(knocking)
Guess who?
(Mrs Davis:)Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)That's right, good job.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)Uh, you wanted
to see me?
(Mrs Davis:)Yes. Uh, welcome back.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I assume you'd like
to reopen our dialogue
(Sheldon:)about the university forcing me
to continue with string theory?
(Mrs Davis:)You mean the dialogue that went,
"Please?" "No." "Please?" "No."
"Please?" "No."
(Sheldon:)That's the one.
(Sheldon:)I believe you went last,
so, uh, please?
(Mrs Davis:)Dr. Cooper, while you were away,
we came up with a solution
(Mrs Davis:)that would allow you to change
your field of study.
(Sheldon:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)Pouting and running away
actually worked.
Yeah, I must say,
that may not be a lesson
(Sheldon:)you want to reinforce with me.
(Sheldon:)So, um, what is the solution?
(Mrs Davis:)Currently, you're being paid
under a grant
(Mrs Davis:)to specifically research
string theory.
(Mrs Davis:)If we promote you
to junior professor,